UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1996 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Photo negatives and Contact Sheets -- 1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Photo negatives and contact sheets -- 1997 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Unlabeled Photo negatives and Contact sheets (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Officials (Box 20, Folder 1)
  unlabeled group photo -- 1 photograph
- Joint council of Cloak and Out-Of-Town (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Poster in Chinese (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Poster in Chinese (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Local 23-25 UNITE Retirees (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). Local 23-25. Photographs (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Education Directors from the Affiliates meet with ILGWU Staff at George Meany Center for Labor Studies (Box 21, Folder 1)
  photos used on a bulletin board display, all mounted on boards -- 72 photographs
- Twenty-Ninth Convention ILGWU, AFL-CIO - Atlantic City, NJ - May 10-18, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 1)